http://www.intelligentnutrients.com/privacy-policy/

Privacy Policy
- Intelligent Nutrients
JavaScript seems to be disabled in your browser.
You must have JavaScript enabled in your browser to utilize the functionality of this website.
0
Your Shopping Cart is empty.
Hair Care
Shampoo ConditionerHair SprayTreatmentsStylingToolsBy ConcernAdd VolumeAdd ShineControl FrizzCreate TextureDefine CurlDry ScalpFine HairOily HairPollution ProtectionPreserve ColorProvide HoldRepair DamageThinning HairBy CollectionHarmonic®PureLuxe™PurePlenty®PureServe®
Best Sellers
Gifts & Sets
Mini Sizes
Add Body with PurePlenty®
Shop Hair Care
Skin Care
Body CareBug RepellentCleanseExfoliateLip CareMoisturizeSanitizerSupplementsTonerTreatmentsBy ConcernAcneAge PreventionCombination SkinDry SkinEnhance RadianceFine Lines & WrinklesMinimize Dark CirclesOily SkinSensitive SkinSkin Care RegimensBy CollectionDestress Express®Intellimune®OneBody®Plant Stem Cell Science®Smart Armor®
Best Sellers
Gifts & Sets
Mini Sizes
Best Selling Skincare Sets
Shop Skin Care
Essential Oils
Body AromaElixirs + OilsHome CareBy CollectionDestress Express®Spirit Essence®
Best Sellers
Gifts & Sets
Mini Sizes
Discover Spirit Essence®
Multi-Use Sanitizer
Shop Essential Oils
Lifestyle
Bug Repellent Home CareSanitizerSupplementsBy CollectionIntellimune®Smart Armor®
Best Sellers
Mini Sizes
Antioxidant Supplements
Smart Armor® Perfume Serum
Shop All Lifestyle
Sets & Kits
About IN
About IN
0
Your Shopping Cart is empty.
Gifts
Gift SetsUnder $30E-Gift Card
Best Sellers
Hair CareSkin CareEssential OilsLifestyleGifts
Hair Care
Shampoo ConditionerHair SprayTreatmentsStylingToolsBy ConcernAdd VolumeAdd ShineControl FrizzCreate TextureDefine CurlDry ScalpFine HairOily HairPollution ProtectionPreserve ColorProvide HoldRepair DamageThinning HairBy CollectionHarmonic®PureLuxe™PurePlenty®PureServe®
Skin Care
Body CareBug RepellentCleanseExfoliateLip CareMoisturizeSanitizerSupplementsTonerTreatmentsBy ConcernAcneAge PreventionCombination SkinDry SkinEnhance RadianceFine Lines & WrinklesMinimize Dark CirclesOily SkinSensitive SkinSkin Care RegimensBy CollectionDestress Express®Intellimune®OneBody®Plant Stem Cell Science®Smart Armor®
Essential Oils
Body AromaElixirs + OilsHome CareBy CollectionDestress Express®Spirit Essence®
Lifestyle
Bug Repellent Home CareSanitizerSupplementsBy CollectionIntellimune®Smart Armor®
Sets & Kits
About IN
My Account
Customer Service
1-800-311-5635
9:00 am to 5:00 pm CST Monday to Friday (Excluding Holidays)
Email Customer Service
Home
Privacy Policy
Privacy Policy
Intelligent Nutrients respects your personal privacy. This web site privacy policy explains how Intelligent Nutrients collects, uses and discloses the personal information you may provide us while using the web site (www.intelligentnutrients.com). You always have the right to refuse the disclosure of any personal information, however, it may inhibit your ability to use the site to its fullest potential including but not limited to online transactions. If we request any personal information, we will disclose the purposes for which we intend to use that information. Your personal information is not lent or sold to anyone for any purpose.
By using the Web Site, you signify your consent to Intelligent Nutrient’s collection, use and disclosure of your personal information in accordance with this Policy.
Non-Identifiable Information This Web Site automatically collects certain non-identifiable information regarding its users, including but not limited to internet protocol addresses, browser type, internet service provider, referring/exit pages, platform type, date and time of pages accessed, time spent on individual pages within the site, and number of pages viewed during your visit. Intelligent Nutrients uses this data, in aggregate form, to improve the online experience for all visitors. We may, on occasion, provide portions of this aggregate data to vendors, consultants, or other third-party agencies.
Voluntary Information During your use of the Web Site, you may be asked to voluntarily provide certain personal information including but not limited to your name, email address, postal address, telephone number and credit card information. You may refuse to provide this information, but doing so may limit your use of this Web Site, including the ability to place orders online.
Intelligent Nutrients may use your personal information to contact and correspond with you, to respond to your inquiries, to process transactions and payments, for marketing purposes, and to facilitate and enhance your use of the Web Site. Intelligent Nutrients may keep a record of all correspondence with you along with your purchasing history. Only Intelligent Nutrients employees and contracted companies with proper authorization will have access to your personal information, and only to the extent necessary for the purposes described in this policy.
Disclosure of personal information In order to process transactions, Intelligent Nutrients must disclose some of your personal information to certain providers, such as your credit card issuer, the product handler and delivery service. Before personal information is disclosed, the service provider will agree with Intelligent Nutrients to protect the privacy of your personal information in a manner that is consistent with this policy. If you do not want Intelligent Nutrients to provide your personal information to our service providers, you may not use the web site for transactions.
Use of Information Collected In accordance with federal law, Intelligent Nutrients may disclose your personal information to a government institution that has asserted its lawful authority to obtain the information or where Intelligent Nutrients has reasonable grounds to believe the information could be useful in the investigation of unlawful activity, or to comply with a subpoena or warrant or an order made by a court, person or body with jurisdiction, or to comply with court rules regarding the production of records and information, or to Intelligent Nutrients legal council.
Reviewing Information Collected You may request access to your personal information and information about Intelligent Nutrients’ collection, use and disclosure of that information by contacting Intelligent Nutrients at customerservice@intelligentnutrients.com. Subject to certain exceptions prescribed by law, you have the right to have reasonable access to your personal information, and have the right to challenge the accuracy and completeness of the information and to have it amended as appropriate. You can help Intelligent Nutrients maintain the accuracy of your information by notifying Intelligent Nutrients of any changes to your personal information.
Transfer of Information Customer lists and information are properly considered assets of a business. Accordingly, if we merge with another entity or if we sell our assets to another entity, our customer lists and information, including personally identifiable information you have provided us, would be included among the assets that would be transferred.
Marketing Certain pages of the web site encourage users to share their experiences with Intelligent Nutrients' products. Intelligent Nutrients is not responsible for the content or claims made in content created by Web Site users. You are not obligated to engage in interactive discussions or provide any personal information during those discussions. Personal information you choose to provide during interactive discussions through the web site will be used and disclosed in accordance with this policy.
When contests or promotions are made available through the Web Site, the applicable contest or promotion rules may include rules regarding the collection, use and disclosure of personal information. To the extent that those specific rules conflict with this policy, the particular contest or promotion rules will govern regarding personal information collection in connection with the contest or promotion.
Links This web site may contain links to other Web Sites or internet resources. When you click on one of those links you are contacting another resource, of which Intelligent Nutrients has no responsibility or liability for or control over those Web Sites.
SMS/MMS MOBILE MESSAGING MARKETING PROGRAM We respect your privacy. We will only use information you provide through the Program to transmit your mobile messages and respond to you, if necessary. This includes, but is not limited to, sharing information with platform providers, phone companies, and other vendors who assist us in the delivery of mobile messages. WE DO NOT SELL, RENT, LOAN, TRADE, LEASE, OR OTHERWISE TRANSFER FOR PROFIT ANY PHONE NUMBERS OR CUSTOMER INFORMATION COLLECTED THROUGH THE PROGRAM TO ANY THIRD PARTY. Nonetheless, We reserve the right at all times to disclose any information as necessary to satisfy any law, regulation or governmental request, to avoid liability, or to protect Our rights or property. When you complete forms online or otherwise provide Us information in connection with the Program, you agree to provide accurate, complete, and true information. You agree not to use a false or misleading name or a name that you are not authorized to use. If, in Our sole discretion, We believe that any such information is untrue, inaccurate, or incomplete, or you have opted into the Program for an ulterior purpose, We may refuse you access to the Program and pursue any appropriate legal remedies.
California Civil Code Section 1798.83 permits Users of the Program that are California residents to request certain information regarding our disclosure of the information you provide through the Program to third parties for their direct marketing purposes. To make such a request, please contact us at the following address:
Intelligent Nutrients
983 East Hennepin Avenue
Minneapolis, Minnesota 55414
customerservice@intelligentnutrients.com
Policy Changes
To accommodate changes in the Web Site, changing technology, and legal developments, this policy may be changed at the sole discretion of Intelligent Nutrients without any prior notice or liability to you or any other person new versions of this plicy will be posted here.
If you have any questions about this policy, please contact Intelligent Nutrients at customerservice@intelligentnutrients.com.
Be the First to Know
Sign up for newsletters, special offers & more
Be pure.
Customer Service
1-800-311-5635
9:00 am to 5:00 pm CST Monday to Friday (Excluding Holidays)
© 2020 Intelligent Nutrients. All Rights Reserved.
Privacy Policy
Terms of Use
Certified means safer, for you, for your earth.
Join Our Cause + Special Offers + Events + Beauty Tips & Tricks
Applies to new email subscribers only. One time offer will be sent via email. Your email is safe with us, privacy matters
You appear to be visiting from United States.
If this is not your country, please select your country below:
